Research and Dean of Graduate Studies, Office of the Vice President for; Records ua400
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 1992 July 17 addition, 1974-1992; 9.57 cubic ft.
  - Dr. Nuala McGann Drescher Affirmative Action Leave Program, 1990 February 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - New Faculty Development Awards Memoranda and Correspondence, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NYS/UUP - New Faculty Correspondence, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Revised Faculty Development Award Program, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Administrative Records, 1993 January 5 addition, 1983-1992; 4.4 cubic ft.
  Folders in this series were maintained in their original order upon processing. As collection was not transferred chronologically, items within the collection are not in chronological order.
  This series contains information on internal audits of the Office's budget, animal research policies, correspondence with research centers and institutes, reports from committees on which the Office played a part and correspondence with academic departments regarding their graduate programs.
  - Africa, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Internal Audit, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - International Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - International Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Middle States Site Visit, 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - International Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - International Programs Tuition Plus, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University of the West Indies Joint Program Proposal, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brazilian Consortium Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University of Manila Records, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - University of Belgrade Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SOMTAD MBA/MPA Program Correspondence [1 of 2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - SOMTAD MBA/MPA Program Correspondence [2 of 2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - SOMTAD MBA/MPA Program Correspondence [1 of 2], 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - SOMTAD MBA/MPA Program Correspondence [2 of 2], 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Animal Care, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Animal Care, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Animal Welfare Complaint, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ASRC Personnel, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must be reviewed by an archivist because of the potential for personally identifiable information.
  - Institute for the Study of Information Science, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Admissions/ Graduate Studies, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Indirect Cost Negotiations, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Discretionary Increases, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - School of Public Health Sciences, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dean - School of Education, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Research Foundation, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - OR5 Allocation, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Joint Laboratories for Advanced Materials, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Applied Science Committee Meetings, Reports + Recommendations, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - President Management Committee, 1989 May-1990 February (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - President Management Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - President Management Committee, 1990 March-1990 April (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Vice Presidents' Meetings, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Center on Campus Priorities (ACCP), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Council of Deans, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Council on Educational Policy, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Council of Graduate Schools in the U.S., 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Academic Council, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Academic Council, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Great Lakes Research Consortium, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Great Lakes Research Consortium, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - National Association Of State Universities and Land- Grant Colleges, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dean College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Art, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Classics, 1983-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - English, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - French Studies, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - German, 1984-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hispanic + Italian Studies, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Linguistics, 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NYS Theater Institute, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Philosophy, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Slavic Studies, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Institute of Cypriot Studies, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Theater, 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Women's Studies, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Center for Arts + Humanities, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Center for German Speech Islands, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Institute for Research on Women, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Dean - College of Science + Math, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Atmospheric Science, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Biological Sciences, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Chemistry, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Computer Science, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Geological Sciences, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mathematics, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Physics, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Physics, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Center for Biochemistry + Biophysics, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Center for Molecular Genetics, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Center for X-Ray Optics, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Biomolecular Stereodynamics, 1981-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Adenine Press, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Programming and Logics, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dean - College of Social & Behavioral Sciences, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - College of Social + Behavioral Sciences, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Africana Studies, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Anthropology, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Communications, 1982-1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Economics, 1983-1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Geography, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - History, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Psychology, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sociology, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - School Psychology, 1985-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Center for Latin American & Caribbean Studies, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Center for Neural, Behav. And Developmental Toxicology, 1985-1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Center for Social and Demographic Research, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Center for Stress and Anxiety Disorder, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Administrative Records, 1994 August 11 addition, 1986-1992; 4 cubic ft.
  This series consists of correspondence relating to the creation of a variety of research centers and institutes, memorandum regarding graduate student recruitment and travel guidelines, departmental employee salary information as well as meeting minutes for a number of committees with which the office was associated.
  Folders in this series were maintained in their original order.
  - Rockefeller College, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Camp Liberty (Professional Development Program), 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Professional Development Programs, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dean - School of Criminal Justice, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - School of Library + Information Science, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dean - Graduate School of Public Affairs, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Center for Legislative Development, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Political Science, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - School of Social Welfare, 1982-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Center for Computing and Disability, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Film and Television Documentation Center Proposal, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hindelang Criminal Justice Research Center, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Inst. For the Study of Information Science (ISIS), 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Traffic Safety, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ringel institute of Gerontology, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - University Center for Policy Research, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dean - School of Business, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Decision Technology Group, 1981-1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - School of Education, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Pre-K Program, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Filmdex Part II, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Counseling Psychology and Student Development, 1983-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Educational Administration, 1985-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Educational Psych + Stats, 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Educational Theory + Practice, 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Educational Management Institute, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CASDA, 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Child Study Research Center, 1982-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Two Year College Development Center, 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - School of Public Health Sciences, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - International Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - China, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Nankai/PhD Sociology, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Somalia SOMTAD, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Telex Services - University @ Albany, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ASRC, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Presidents, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - VP Academic Affairs, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Travel, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Student Travel, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Student Travel, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Student Travel Fund Program, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Student Travel Request, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Student Travel Program, 1989-1990; 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Recruitment Subcommittee Spring, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Recruitment Subcommittee, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Minority Recruitment Subcommittee, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Recruit/Retention Subcommittee, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Admissions Review Committee, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Benevolent Association Fellowships Fall Winners, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Benevolent Association Fellowships Spring Winners, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Benevolent Association Fellowships Background, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Benevolent Association Fellowship Spring Winners, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Benevolent Association Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Benevolent Association Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - SUNY Benevolent Awards Fall, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Benevolent Awards Fall, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - SUNY Benevolent Awards Spring, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - SUNY Benevolent Awards Spring/Summer, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Benevolent Association Awards Fall, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Benevolent Association Awards Fall, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Benevolent Association Awards Spring, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Benevolent Association Fall, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Benevolent Association Awards Spring, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Distinguished Service Professor, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Distinguished Service Professor Selection Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - MACC Fall, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Employee Assistance Program, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Discretionary Salary, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - OR-5 Discretionary, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - OR-5 Discretionary, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Discretionary Increases, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Discretionary Increases, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Discretionary Salary Increases (88-89 yr of consider), 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Council on Research, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Council on Research, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Council on Research, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Journals & Conferences, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Request for Journal and Conference Financial Support [1 of 2], 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Request for Journal and Conference Financial Support [2 of 2], 1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Journals & Conferences Committee Spring, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Research Incentives, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Excellence in Research, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Research Awards Program, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Research Awards Program Application Cycle, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - FRAP Final Reports Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Administrative Records, 1995 January 23 addition, 1983-1992; 2 cubic ft.
  This series is primarily focused on graduate research policies, office correspondence, graduate fellowship guidelines and Research Initiative memorandums.
  Files in this series were maintained in their original order upon transfer.
  - SUNY Doctoral Council, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Research Office, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Research Foundation, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Research Foundation Senior Management Meeting SUNY Plaza, Room T- 401, 1990 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Research Foundation, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Research Foundation, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Space Grant Program, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Strategic Defense Initiative (SDI), 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Research Safety, 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Research Building, 1983-1985; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Enrollment Management Committee Spring, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Internal Control Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Education and Research Initiative (GRI), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Education and Research Initiative (GRI), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - (GRI), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Research Initiative, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Graduate Education and Research Initiative (GRI), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Academic Equipment Replacement, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Assistantship/Fellowship Tax, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Assistantship/Fellowship, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Assistant/Teaching Assistant, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Minority Recruitment, 1982-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Underrepresented Graduate Fellowship, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - International Program [1 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - International Program [2 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Studies/ Grad. Admissions, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Material Diagnostics, Inc. (H. Bakhru), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cartermill Agreement, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gallup-Primate, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Letters/Memos Written, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Top File, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Administrative Records, 1997 May 15 addition, 1982-1995; 9 cubic ft.
  This series contains documentation of research and faculty awards including FRAP, correspondence with academic departmnets and several university collectives, as well as minutes, memoranda and correspondence related to graduate program development and various committees and university consortiums with which the Office of Research and Graduate Studies was affiliated with. This series also contains correspodence between the Office of Research and similar offices at different colleges in the SUNY system.
  - Graduate Student Union, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GRI Postdoctoral Positions, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Confidentiality, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Assistantships/Fellowships, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Assistants/ Teaching Assistants, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Education Forum for Students of Color, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minority Recruitment, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Moscow State U, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Underrepresented Grad Fellowship, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Int'l Assistantships/Fellowships, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Middle States Association, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Tuition, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Council on Research, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Council on Research, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Council on Research Incentives, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Research Incentives, 1990 June-1992 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Centers & Institutes, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Centers & Institutes, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Committee on External Linkages, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Safety Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cf + Jrnls - Support Ltr., 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Journals & Conference Support Considerations, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Journals / Conferences Requests, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - FRAP, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - FRAP Final Reports Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - FRAP, 1992-1993; 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - FRAP, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - FRAP Final Reports Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Excellence in Research, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Excellence in Research, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Excellence in Research Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Excellence in Research, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Misconduct in Research Policy Development, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - University Design Committee Spring, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Benevolent Grant Awards Competition Spring, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Benevolent Grant Awards Fall, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Benevolent Association Awards Spring, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Distinguished Service Professor Selection Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Disclosure Statement (General Correspondence), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Disclosure Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Disclosure Statement (General Correspondence), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Disclosure Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Disclosure Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Council of Graduate Schools [ 1 of 3 ], 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Council of Graduate Schools [ 2 of 3 ], 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Council of Graduate Schools [ 3 of 3 ], 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - General Education Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Academic Council, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Great Lakes, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hudson-Mohawk Association of Colleges and Universities, 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - NASULGC, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - National Sciences Foundation, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Openmind Association, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Programs Advisory Council, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Technology Resource Sharing Group, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - University Corp. for Atmos. Research, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - University Mission--- Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - University Recruitment and Retention Group, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Vice Presidents Meeting [1 of 3], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Vice Presidents Meeting [2 of 3], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Vice Presidents Meeting [3 of 3], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Lightning Detection Work, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - EPRI/NLDN, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Research Foundation EPRI/NLDN, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - EPRI/NLDN, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - EPRI (Longo Proposal), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NLDN/EPRI, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - SUNY Chancellor, 1986-1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Academic Programs Policy and Planning, 1982-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Executive Vice Chancellor, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Employee Relations and Educ. Services, 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Finance and Business, 1987-1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Health Sciences, 1982-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Education and Research, 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - University Committee for Applied Science, 198-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Vice Chancellor for Information Technology, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Institutional Research and Planning, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Vice Chancellor for Int'l Planning, 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Office of the Provost, 1986-1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs and Special Programs, 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Academic Policy Group, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Advisory Committee on Campus Priorities, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Amer. Council on ED, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Capital Region Technology Council Development, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Council on Educational Policy [1 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Council on Educational Policy [2 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda [1 of 3], 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda [2 of 3], 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda [3 of 3], 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda [1 of 3], 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda [2 of 3], 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda [3 of 3], 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ringel Institute, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Geological Science, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Biological Sciences, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Atmospheric Science, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Physics, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Physics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Army Environmental Policy Institute (relocation of), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CAT- Thank You's List, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Center for Advanced Technology (CAT Program), 1983; 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CAT, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CAT, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - CAT- Center for Advanced Technology, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - New York State Science and Technology Foundation - Board of Directors Meetings, 1994 April 27 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NYSERDA Promotional Materials and Reports, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NYS Energy Research and Development Authority (NYSERDA, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - DHHS Audit, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - RF Audit, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Research Foundation, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Research Foundation, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Research Office, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - DOCT Mailing Lists, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - A21, 1979-1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Animal Care, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Research Foundation Decentralization Project, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Howard Hughes Proposal, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Incubator Facility Initiative, 1982-1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Indirect Costs [1 of 3], 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Indirect Costs [2 of 3], 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Indirect Costs [3 of 3], 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Research Advisory Council, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - RF/IDC/OR-5 Budget, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - ASRC Memos and Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Office International Programs Memoranda Administrative Records [1 of 2], 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Office International Programs Memoranda Administrative Records [2 of 2], 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Internal Audit, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sponsored Funds, 1987-1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Sciences College of, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Science Dean, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Africana Studies, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Anthropology, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Biological Sciences, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Communication, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)